(air whooshes)
- [Narrator] Journal Update award
for best writing or story.
- [Speaker 1] The captain
wants you up on deck.
- [Narrator] Divinity: Original Sin.
- [Speaker 2] Them gulls,
means we're close to shore.
(waves crashing)
I don't envy ya going there,
Master (indistinct).
- New kid,
we wanna thank you for
helping us determine
whether or not Monica
was a two-faced bitch.
She really made us mad,
but it turns out she
couldn't have been the one
spreading rumors about Allie Nelson
going to the abortion clinic.
- Yeah!
- To solve this before
something else happens.
- [Narrator] The Wolf Among Us.
- [Speaker 3] This is bigger
than what I thought it was.
And I didn't see it, didn't see...
- [Speaker 4] (indistinct) erosion.
- All of you,
- [Narrator] The Walking Dead:
- just put your guns down.
- [Narrator] Season 2.
- This will be fine.
- We have a baby.
(baby cries)
- [Speaker 5] You have a baby with you?
- [Speaker 6] I'm so sorry,
Red.
- [Narrator] Transistor.
- [Speaker 6] They took your
voice. I couldn't stop them.
- [Narrator] And the winner is
South Park: The Stick of Truth,
written by Matt and Trey, themselves,
South Park: The Stick of Truth
was probably one of the best transitions
from televised series to
video game we've seen yet.
There's been a small
handful of South Park games
in the past that the duo just
passed off to the developers,
and the quality showed.
This time, however, things were different.
Working hands-on with the developers,
Matt Stone and Trey
Parker wrote the script
to probably the most crass
and hilarious game this year.
Stick of Truth went
directions many developers
are afraid to take,
and the result paid off.
(air whooshes)